highlights.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy and Security - Highlights.com

By Age

By Category

Fun for Families

|  | 

**Highlights for Children's Online Privacy Notice**

For more than 60 years, we at Highlights for Children have developed relationships with our customers based upon respect and integrity. We're aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when providing us with information. This notice describes our online privacy policy. We promise to treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity we have displayed throughout our history. By visiting Highlights.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Online Privacy Notice. 

**Application:**

This privacy policy applies only to Highlights.com and its affiliated promotional web sites. This policy does not apply to HighlightsKids.com nor any of our offline promotions. To view the privacy policy for HighlightsKids.com, please click [here.](http://www.highlightskids.com/admin/ps_f_privacyPolicy.asp)

For information pertaining to our offline privacy policy, please click here or make a request via e-mail at [profile@highlights.com](mailto:profile@highlights.com)

**Contact Us:**

Highlights for Children  
Business Office  
1800 Watermark Drive  
P.O. Box 269   
Columbus, OH 43216   
(614) 486-0631   

Highlights for Children  
Editorial Office  
803 Church Street  
Honesdale, PA 18431  
(570) 253-1080  

**Changes to this Privacy Notice:**

This Privacy Notice will change over time. Please check this page periodically as you continue to use our site to see if any changes have been made. This privacy notice was most recently changed on July, 2003. 

**Personal Information Collected by Highlights.com:**

The information we collect from our visitors helps us to personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Highlights.com. We gather the following types of information: 

**Automatic Information:**

When you visit our web site, we recognize the domain name of your ISP (Internet Service Provider)via an Internet Protocol (IP) address. We do not recognize individual users, but we do know if visitors are connecting to the internet from popular ISPs like AOL, MSN, Earthlink, or a private company network. 

We also track various tallies of website traffic. Examples include computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) which lead to and around our site; and the pages viewed on our sites, including the date and time of visits. We collect and analyze this information to improve the content, navigation, and performance of our web site. 

Like many Web sites, we use "cookies" ("cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your hard drive through your Web browser to maintain information during your visit). For example, if you are a registered user, we use cookies to maintain your account information, history, and/or site preferences when you sign-in. Your browser allows you to reject cookies, and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our web site anonymously, although certain site functionalities may be impacted. 

**Information You Give Us:**  

We collect information you enter on our web site. This information is normally provided when you place an order (establish an account) or contact us. Examples of the types of supplied information include your name, address, telephone number, credit card information, and e-mail address. We use this information for such purposes as to confirm an order, ship product, billing and marketing/promotional initiatives. For more information regarding the use of e-mail addresses, and how we share information with other parties, please see below. 

When you sign-in to your Highlights.com account, you can review the information you have provided to us, and update or delete such information. 

**How We Use E-mail Addresses:**

Whenever we request your e-mail address, we tell you if the request is optional or mandatory. Every time we prompt for an e-mail address, we give you the opportunity to decide whether or not you want to receive e-mail promotions from Highlights. The following are some examples of how we use the e-mail addresses we collect: 

  * To confirm receipt of an online order 
  * To e-mail an online newsletter 
  * To send e-mail announcements and promotions 
  * To identify the author of postings to our message boards 
  * To answer customer service, product, and general inquiries 
  * To notify you about updates to the site

If you have elected to receive e-mail announcements and promotions and wish at any time to no longer receive such information, please call (614) 486-0631 or send e-mail to [profile@highlights.com](mailto:profile@highlights.com). You will receive confirmation that your e-mail address has been removed from our announcement list. Please remember that removal requests are individual e-mail address specific. And while we will do our best to implement your preference change as quickly as possible, you may continue to receive promotional e-mails briefly after making your opt-out request. 

**Sharing of Information with Third Parties:**

**_Third Party Marketing Partners:_** We may employ other companies or individuals to perform certain services/functions on our behalf. Examples include: sending e-mail, analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties may have access to personal information; however, these independent contractors will be legally bound to use the information to perform only those functions designated by Highlights and NOT for any other purpose.

 **Bulletin Board, Parents Poll, and Discussion List Policy:**

Our message boards are moderated. This means that we read all messages before public posting. We do not edit messages, but we may decide not to post a message we deem inappropriate for any reason. The opinions expressed on our message boards do not necessarily represent the views of Highlights for Children 

When you participate in one of our polls, we tally and report the results on an aggregated basis. We cannot track the responses of individual participants. These are informal polls offered for you to share your opinions with others. Highlights for Children does not endorse poll results, nor do we make claims of any statistical validity. 

**Purchase Security:**

When we prompt you for credit card information, we encrypt the number for security. This is called Secure Socket Layer. Your credit information is handled by established third party banking and processing agents under contract to Highlights for Children. 

**Children:**

Highlights.com does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Highlights.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

 **Business Transfer:**

In the unlikely event that Highlights for Children is sold, has substantially all of its assets acquired, or merges or becomes affiliated with any other individual or entity, any and all customer information owned or under the control of Highlights may be one of the transferred assets. 

**Law Enforcement and Protection of Users:**

We will release personal information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate to do so to comply with the law. We will also do so to cooperate with law enforcement investigations, comply with court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us or others, when we believe the safety of a person may be in jeopardy, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/or credit risk reduction. 

**Links to Third Party Sites:**

Our web site contains links to third party sites. Highlights for Children is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these sites. We suggest you check and fully understand the privacy policy of each site you visit.

|
